golivewire.com 2003-02-08

# LiveWire Teen Forums & College Forums - Privacy Policy

Your privacy is very important to us. LiveWire Forums will store a few details about you while you are using our website. LiveWire Forums takes all reasonable steps to ensure that no unauthorized access to your information is allowed. You do not have to register on our website to use it. LiveWire Forums only requires you to register if you wish to post material or messages to the LiveWire Forums website. When you register at LiveWire Forums, we collect some information from you, such as your date of birth, location, and email address. You can update your information at anytime by accessing My Account. 

We do not register people under the age of 13. If you are under 13, we request that you come back and visit us when you are teen. LiveWire Forums does not knowingly register users under the age of 13 nor does LiveWire Forums knowingly collect personally identifiable information from those under 13. If LiveWire Forums receives credible information that a registered user is under 13, LiveWire Forums will remove personally identifiable information and close the account. 

If you do register on LiveWire Forums, you will have a password. LiveWire Forums will make every reasonable effort to protect your password. You are responsible for keeping your password confidential. Do not share it. If you share a computer with other people, make sure that when you leave, you sign out of LiveWire Forums. 

Be careful about sharing personal information in public places. If you send personal information through email, or post it on a message board or in a private message, then other people can collect it and use it. You may end up receiving email messages you do not want from people you do not know. 

We may release your personal information if required by law, or if we have cause to believe that it might stop someone from harming others. 

The following information is collected: 

**Cookies**   
LiveWire will set the following cookies: 

Membername: This is so LiveWire Forums can remember your membername when using the website. This cookie is called 'amembernamecookie'. 

Password: This is so you don't have to re-type in your password everytime you wish to make a post or use any of the member only features on the board. This cookie is called 'apasswordcookie'. 

**IP address**   
When you register and when you make a post your IP address is stored on our server. This protects you as a user and us as an organization when identifying that the user who posted is indeed authentic. This information will only be used if you misuse any features on the board or in any dispute. LiveWire is able to ban a member by the member's IP address. 

**Registration Form**   
The registration process is designed so that you can keep a unique identity. Your year of birth will be kept private and your email address and other contact information will only be available to LiveWire Moderators and LiveWire Administrators. LiveWire Forums will take all reasonable measures to ensure that any information you provide confidentially is kept confidential. You may change this information at any time by accessing My Account. 

**Postings**   
LiveWire Forums and its administrators cannot be held responsible for the content of posted messages on the forums or private messages sent from one user to another user. 

**Bulletin Board Security**   
Ikonboard.com being the authors of this Bulletin Board software have taken all reasonable steps to ensure that there is sufficient security in place to stop external misuse of any and all information that you provide. 

**How to contact us**   
You are invited to email LiveWire at [webmaster@golivewire.com](mailto:webmaster@golivewire.com)

Modified August 17th, 2002 

« Back
